 Instructions:
 
 1. Create BYOND account
 2. https://help.github.com/articles/set-up-git -> Download GitHub for Windows
 3. Install the downloaded app
 4. Log in / set up app
 5. When that is done, go to the dashboard and under repositories there should be local and github.  
	Under github there should be either my name or yours. Click it, then the YBother repository should be visible. Click CLONE.
 6. open dreammaker.exe (should be in the bin folder wherever you installed BYOND)
 7. open dreamseeker.exe, log in to account
 8. File -> open environment -> go find Generic ARPG.dme (can right click the repository in the github app and hit open in explorer to find the location)
 9. build -> compile, then build -> run (ctrl+k, ctrl+r respectively)
 
 
 If any changes are made, go back to the github app and click local repositories, then the arrow on the YBother. It will list the changes etc. 
 enter a commit message and brief explanation, click commit, then click sync.

  ▲
 ▲ ▲ ~Stygmia